Zak Janzi

QA Engineer | Technical Writer

zakjanzi@hotmail.com <u>Portfolio</u> • <u>Github</u>

Summary

<u>ISTQB certified</u> automation QA Engineer with DevOps experience. Solid background in scripting, full-stack development and infrastructure management. Strong interest in distributed systems and in-depth knowledge of the economic implications of blockchain technology.

Skills

- <u>Languages:</u> Solidity, Java, JavaScript, Python, SQL.
- <u>Technologies:</u> MERN, LAMP, NGINX, AWS, Hardhat.
- Testing frameworks: Cypress, Selenium, Appium, RESTAssured, TestNG.
- <u>Tools:</u> Git, Jenkins, Docker, Grafana, JMeter, Postman, JIRA.

Experience

Lebanese Alternative Learning - Beirut, Lebanon - 9/2023 to Present

SysOps Engineer

- Implemented and maintained security measures to while continuously monitoring the health and performance of servers.
- Kept detailed records of system configurations, procedures in compliance with donor regulations.
- Managed deployments across different physical and virtual environments.
- Contributed to open-source projects (Moodle/IOMAD)

Inbound Square - Remote - 8/2023 to Present

Technical Writer

• Wrote technical articles covering topics related to SaaS/PaaS tools. See the writing section

below for samples.

• Topics include ZK-Proofs, Cloud Loud Testing, Test Environment Management, Non-Functional

<u>Testing</u>, Preview Environments (in progress)

One More Multiverse - Boston, Massachusetts - 10/2021 to 09/2023

Senior Manual QA Engineer

• Designed, developed and executed comprehensive, well-structured test plans and test cases to

ensure software quality.

Recorded, documented and triaged software bugs thoroughly.

• Conducted functional, performance, regression and UAT tests on a regular basis.

• Liaised with QA analysts and contributed to the requirement docs and acceptance criteria.

• Coordinated with product owners for testing plans and feature releases.

Reference: Mike Prentice, QA Lead – mike@playmultiverse.com

Tylleum - Beirut, Lebanon - 08/2022 to 02/2023 (contract)

Automation Tester

Produced and executed automated end-to-end tests for a Web3 mobile app.

• Analyzed software requirements to create high-coverage test cases.

Developed and maintained automated test cases for both iOS and Android.

• Conducted functional and non-functional testing, ensuring comprehensive coverage.

• Identified critical issues and generated defect reports for prompt resolution.

Worked closely with cross-functional teams to ensure a holistic approach to quality.

Maintained thorough records of test cases, results, and scripts.

Conducted load and other non-functional tests.

Reference: Dani Nehme, CTO - dani@tylleum.com

Education

B.S - Entrepreneurial Management, Class of 2018

Lebanese American University - Beirut, Lebanon

Projects (link to portfolio)

- <u>BIP39 JavaScript Implementation:</u> A JavaScript implementation of a cryptocurrency wallet generator.
- <u>A Quantum Proof Server:</u> A quantum resistance NGINX web server for when quantum computers take over the world.
- <u>End-to-End Testing Framework</u>: A suite of automated tests for an E-Bank using Selenium and TestNG.
- <u>A Python Scraper:</u> A script that scrapes the value of the LBP against the USD at the shadow market rate, then stores it in a DB.
- <u>A Company Site</u>: A static website for a client.
- Conway's Game of Life

Additional Information

- EU National.
- Trilingual